transitionbikes.com 2008-11-12

# Transition Bikes Privacy Policy

Transition Bikes Privacy Policy
By visiting transitionbikes.com you agree to accept the practices described
in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to this Privacy Notice, Conditions of Use and Notices:
This Privacy Policy may change over time and the use of information which
we gather now is subject to these Notices as modified. If you visit our web
site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice,
including the application of the laws of the State of Washington.
Personal Information Collected By Transition Bikes:
Transition Bikes uses information that we collect from our visitors to
personalize and improve your visit at transitionbikes.com. We gather the
following types of information:
Information you give us: Transition Bikes collects any information which
you enter on our Web site. Examples of the type of information you may
supply us with include your name, address, telephone number, credit card
information and e-mail addresses.
Automatic Information collected by us: Whenever you visit our Web site
we collect and temporarily store (for the duration of your visit)
information such as "cookies" which remember information about a visitor
from one page to the next and from one visit to the next. We collect and
analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet;
login; password; computer and connection information such as your
browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase
history; the URLs which lead you to and around our Web site including the
date and time; the pages you viewed. Your browser allows you to reject
cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to
visit our Web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at
our Web site if you use this software but we will not be able to offer you
our personalized services.
Orders: If you place an order we use a secure order form which requires
you to provide contact, billing, and financial information.
Sharing of Information:
The protection of your personal information is very important to Transition
Bikes and we will never share your personal information except for those
conditions listed below.
Credit card companies and shippers: When you buy something from us we
send your credit card information, name, billing address and the amount
of your purchase to your credit card company to verify and authorize the
purchase. Your name, telephone number and shipping information must be
provided to third party shippers such as UPS, and the United States Postal
Service to deliver your purchase.
Law Enforcement and Protection of Users: We will release personally
identifiable information to third parties and organizations only when we
believe it is appropriate for us to do so to comply with the law. We will

also do so to cooperate with law enforcement investigations, comply with
court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or
when we believe it is needed for fraud protection.
Security:
Our Web site protects the security of personal information you transmit to
us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts
information you input. We do not reveal your credit card number when we
confirm your order. In order to protect against unauthorized access to
your account you should sign off when you finish visiting our site/placing
an order.
